Guide to the K. Leroy Irvis Papers, 1946-1995 AIS.1971.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Political Activities, 1962-1996; X.
  - House of Representatives, Law Suits, etc. (1995 Addition), 1971-1994; 3.
    - Minority Studies (Box 74, Folder 212)
    - Multicultural Education (Box 74, Folder 213)
    - NAACP (Box 74, Folder 214)
    - National Conference of State Legislatures (NCSL), 1978 (Box 74, Folder 215)
    - Newsletters - Various (Box 75, Folder 216)
    - New York State Legislature (Box 75, Folder 217)
    - Pennsylvania Economy League, Inc. (Box 75, Folder 218)
    - House Bills (Box 75, Folder 219)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives- Correspondence (Box 75, Folder 220)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives- Calendar, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 221)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives- Pamphlets on various rules in House (Box 75, Folder 222)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives- Financing Agency, 1979, 1984-1988 (Box 75, Folder 223)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives- Various, 1971, 1976, 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 224)
    - Pennsylvania House of Representatives- Citation Achievement (Box 76, Folder 225)
    - PA State Legislature (Box 76, Folder 226)
    - Political Booklets (Box 76, Folder 227)
    - Remarks/Speakers (Box 76, Folder 228)
    - Rose, Schmidt, and Dixon (Box 76, Folder 229)
    - Sickov and Love (Box 76, Folder 230)
    - Reports - Various (Box 76, Folder 231)
    - Teleprompter Cable Bribe Allegation, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 232)
    - Three Rivers Improvement Project (TRIAD) (Box 76, Folder 233)
    - Various Correspondence, 1983-1994 (Box 76, Folder 234)
    - Voter Registration (Box 76, Folder 235)
    - Watson, Bill (Box 76, Folder 236)
  - Political Organizations and Conventions (1995 Addition), 1968-1988; 4.
    This subseries contains convention packets from Democratic National Conventions, 1968-1988, and correspondence, newsletters, and publications from political organizations including the Pennsylvania Legislative Black Caucus and Pennsylvania Democratic Committee. This subseries is arranged chronologically by subject.
    - Democratic National Convention- Souvenirs, Maps, etc., 1968, 1984, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 178)
    - Democratic National Convention- Chicago, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 179-181)
    - Democratic National Convention- San Francisco, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 182-183)
    - Democratic National Convention- San Francisco, 1983-1984 (Box 72, Folder 184)
    - Democratic National Convention- Calendar, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 185)
    - Democratic National Convention- Atlanta, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 186-187)
    - Democratic National Convention- Various Correspondence (Box 72, Folder 188)
    - Democratic National Convention- Black Caucus (Box 72, Folder 189)
    - Pennsylvania Legislative Black Caucus (Box 73, Folder 190)
    - Pennsylvania State Committee (Box 73, Folder 191)
    - Pennsylvania Democratic State Committee (Box 73, Folder 192)
    - Pennsylvania Democratic Party (Box 73, Folder 193)
    - House Democratic Campaign Committee, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 194)
  - Democratic Party Involvement/Conventions (2010 Addition), 1965-1996; 5.
    As a Democratic member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives, Irvis found himself highly involved with the Democratic Party. His involvement garnished correspondence, newsletters, and publications from the party as well as the Democratic National Committee. Since Irvis was highly involved with the DNC, he often served as a delegate at the Democratic National Convention. The materials which pertain to the national conventions are packets, periodicals, brochures, and convention memorabilia. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Allegheny County Democratic Party, 1983-1988 (Box 113, Folder 32)
    - Articles, 1991, undated (Box 113, Folder 33)
    - Candidate Brochures, undated (Box 113, Folder 34)
    - Charters and By-laws, 1984-1991 (Box 113, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1997, undated (Box 113, Folder 36)
    - Democratic National Committee Meeting, 1985 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Democratic National Committee Meeting, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1992 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Democratic National Convention, Co-Chair Orientation, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Democratic National Convention, Credentials Committee, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Democratic National Convention, Passes, 1968, 1984-1985, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Democratic Party of Pennsylvania, 1969-1996 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - La Rouche, Lyndon, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Membership Card and Passes, 1965-1989 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - National Democratic Club, 1988, undated (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Notes, undated (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Presidential Campaign, 1984 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Presidential Poll, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 21)
- Speeches and Interviews, 1969-1991; XI.
  This series consists largely of interviews with Irvis in his last few years as a legislator before his retirement in 1988; these interviews cover all aspects of Irvis's life, including his childhood and family, his education, and his career as a lawyer and a legislator. In addition, there are some transcripts or texts from Irvis's speeches for community and civic organizations, as well as some invitations from groups inviting Irvis to speak and Irvis's correspondence about speaking engagements.
  This series is arranged into three subseries according to the date the material was acquired by the University of Pittsburgh.
  - Speeches, Interviews, Tapes (1971 Original Deposit), 1969-1970; 1.
    This subseries includes speeches, addresses, lectures, and interviews given by Irvis, 1969-1970. These include a speech to the Catholic Diocese of Harrisburg, address to Franklin and Marshall College, and a transcript of a TV interview which was hosted by Warren Dean and a panel of three Pennsylvania journalists, 1970. This series is arranged by subject.
    - Speeches, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 313)
    - Address, Franklin and Marshall College, (Tape and Transcription), October 6, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 314)
    - Urban Politics Lecture, "Black Man in Politics", (Tape Only), no date (Box 20, Folder 314a)
    - Broadcast interview, "Black Perspective on the News", (Tape and Transcript), August 29, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 315)
  - Transcripts from Taped Interviews (1995 Addition), 1981-1987; 2.
    This subseries contains transcripts from taped interviews. Folders 159-162 consist of transcripts of Irvis answering questions that had been sent to him in 1981. Folders 163-177 contain interviews conducted by Janet Patterson, 1986-1987 and include all aspects of Irvis' life including childhood, campaigning, and presidents. These materials are arranged by date of interview.
    - November, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 159-162)
    - May 8, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 163)
    - May 12, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 164)
    - May 14, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 165)
    - May 22, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 166)
    - May 29, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 167)
    - June 29, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 168)
    - June 28, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 169)
    - July 9, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 170)
    - July 22, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 171)
    - September 4, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 172)
    - September 10, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 173)
    - October 3, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 174)
    - April 22, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 175)
    - April 30, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 176)
    - May 7, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 177)
  - Business and Speaking Engagements (1995 Addition), 1980-1991; 3.
    This subseries includes invitations, correspondence, pamphlets, honors, programs, and publications regarding Irvis' business and speaking engagements, 1980-1991. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - International Business Associates (Box 79, Folder 256)
    - Invitations Requesting KLI to Speak (Box 79, Folder 257)
    - Invitations - Various (Box 79, Folder 258)
    - Irvis - Business Correspondence (Box 79, Folder 259)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 260)
    - Pamphlets - Various (Box 79, Folder 261)
    - Park and Ride, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 262)
    - Programs - Honors (Box 80, Folder 263)
    - Programs - Various Speaking Engagements (Box 80, Folder 264)
    - Programs - Various (Box 80, Folder 265)
    - Publications - Various (Box 80, Folder 266)
    - Special Engagements - Memorial Services (Box 80, Folder 267)
    - Special Engagements - Schools (Box 80, Folder 268)
- Katharyne Irvis, 1941-1959; XII.
  This series contains materials related to K. Leroy Irvis' first wife, Katharyne (1918-1959). After attending the Tuskegee Institute, Katharyne received a Bachelor of Science from Prairie View College. Kathryne was involved with a wide array of organizations including her career at the Pittsburgh Courier, membership at the Urban League of Pittsburgh, NAACP, National Council of Negro Women, and Democrats for United Action. She was also a skilled tennis player who played competitively and won many titles.
  This series is arranged into two subseries based on the date that the materials were acquired by the University of Pittsburgh.
  - Katharyne Irvis (1980 Addition), 1.
    This subseries documents the many awards and titles Katharyne Irvis won as a tennis player including the National Negro Women's Championship (Doubles - 1942; Singles - 1945), and the American Tennis Association National Women's Singles Title, 1946. She was an advertising rep for the Pittsburgh Courier as well as a member of the Urban League of Pittsburgh, NAACP, National Council of Negro Women, and Democrats for United Action. These records are arranged by subject and include newsclippings, manuscripts, and other materials.
    - Paper on Freedman's Bureau (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Tennis Newspaper Clippings (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Katharyne Irvis (2010 Addition), 1941-1959; 2.
    This subseries includes records relating heavily to Katharyne Irvis' earlier life and education, as well as correspondence from K. Leroy Irvis from the duration of time while they lived at a distance from one another. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - News clippings, undated (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Notebook, Simmons, Andrea, 1941 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Obituary, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - School Diploma, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - School Notes, undated (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - School Notes, undated (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Sketches by Irvis, 1947-1953 (Box 93, Folder 23)
- Cathryn Irvis, 1936-2004; XIII.
  Cathryn, Irvis' second wife, was involved in several organizations including the Women in Urban Crisis, the Million Woman March, the Community College of Allegheny County, the Port Authority of Allegheny County, the Black Women's Political Crusade, the March of Dimes, and the National Association of Negro Business and Professional Women's Club, Inc. In addition to the organizations she was involved in, Mrs. Irvis was also highly involved in the organization of the International Year of the Child. She was a board member of Community College of Allegheny County (CCAC), Port Authority of Allegheny County (PAT), and Redevelopment Authority of Allegheny County, among other organizations. These materials also include information on the Black Women's Political Crusade, Pennsylvania Council for the Arts, and Vote America.
  This series is divided into two subseries based on the date the materials in each were acquired by the University of Pittsburgh.
  - Cathryn Irvis (1995 Addition), 1977-1987; 1.
    This subseries contains correspondence, programs, speeches, awards, and materials regarding Irvis' second wife, Mrs. Cathryn Irvis.
    - Black Women's Political Crusade (BWPC), 1979-1987 (Box 69, Folder 143-146)
    - Cards (Box 69, Folder 147)
    - Carter/Mondale Campaign (Box 69, Folder 148)
    - Community College of Allegheny County (CCAC) (Box 69, Folder 149)
    - Mrs. Irvis, 1980-1983, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 150)
    - Hand in Hand, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 151)
    - Metropolitan Pittsburgh Public Broadcasting (MPPB), 1983 (Box 69, Folder 152)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 153)
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County (PAT), 1971, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 154)
    - Programs, Speeches, Awards (Box 69, Folder 155)
    - Redevelopment Authority of Allegheny County, 1983 (Box 70, Folder 156)
    - United Way, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 157)
    - Vote America, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 158)
  - Cathryn Irvis (2010 Addition), 1936-2004; 2.
    The subseries focuses on Cathryn Irvis, highlights her organizational involvement and is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - APTA, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Awards, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - Awards, 1978, 1995 (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Birthday, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - BWPC By-laws, undated (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - BWPC Employment Opportunities, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - BWPC Events, 1979-1990 (Box 93, Folder 30)
    - BWPC Information, 1979-1985 (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - BWPC Notes, 1985-1988 (Box 93, Folder 32)
    - BWPC Membership, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 33)
    - BWPC Minutes, 1979-1986 (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - BWPC Memorabilia, undated (Box 93, Folder 35)
    - Campaign, 1986-1988 (Box 93, Folder 36)
    - Campaign, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 37)
    - Campaign Finances, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 38)
    - Campaign Finances, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 39)
    - Children's Needs Assessment Handbook, 1979 (Box 93, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1993 (Box 93, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Education, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Education, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Education, Research, 1965-1975 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Education, University of Pittsburgh, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Floods and High Water, 1936 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Harrisburg Area Community College, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Human Rights, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - National Association of Negro Business and Professional Women's Clubs, 1987, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - National Black Catholic Congress, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - National Political Congress of Black Women, Membership Dues, 1993-1994 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - News clippings, 1979-1986 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Newsletters, 1976, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Commission for Women, 1975-1986 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Personal Agenda, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Port Authority of Allegheny County (PAT), 1987 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - PAT, Annual Report, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - PAT, Audit and Finance, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - PAT, Board Minutes, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - PAT, Board Orientation, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - PAT, Board Orientation, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - PAT, By-laws, undated (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - PAT, Disadvantaged Business Program, 1980-1986 (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - PAT, Equal Employment Opportunity Subcommittee, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - PAT, Equal Employment Opportunity Subcommittee, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - PAT, Equal Employment Opportunity Subcommittee, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - PAT, Executive Director Evaluation, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - PAT, Group and Party Requirements, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - United Way of Pennsylvania, Membership Manual, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Women in the Urban Crisis, 1979-1980 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Year of the Child, Contacts, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Year of the Child, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Year of the Child, Mailing Package, 1978-1979 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Photographs, 1947-2005; XIV.
  This series contains photographs relating to Irvis's life and career, including his personal life, hobbies and artistic work, his legislative and legal work, and his speaking engagements, educational work, and civic involvement. Some photographs have associated newsclippings, notes, or other documentation.
  The photoraphs are divided into three subseries based on the date the materials were originally acquired by the University of Pittsburgh.
  - Photographs (1971 Original Deposit), 1963-1971; 1.
    This subseries contains photographs of Irvis at various events. The photos are arranged by alphabetically by subject.
    - KLI-Art exhibits, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 317)
    - KLI-Awards, honors, etc., 1967, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 318)
    - KLI-Bill signings, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 319)
    - KLI-Check presentations, 1968, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 320)
    - KLI-Dedications, memorial services, etc., 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 321)
    - KLI-Miscellaneous legislature, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 322)
    - KLI-Majority Leader, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 323)
    - KLI-Mine inspection, no date (Box 20, Folder 324)
    - KLI-Testimonials (for others), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 325)
    - KLI-with visiting groups, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 326)
    - KLI-Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Box 21, Folder 327)
    - Dixmont State Hospital, 1963, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 328)
    - Political campaigns, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 329)
  - Photographs (1995 Addition), 1958-1988; 2.
    This subseries contains both work and family photographs of K. Leroy Irvis. Some photos (where indicated at folder level notes) include clippings, negatives, and correspondence. Photos containing unknown persons or places are described by "?". This series is arranged by subject.
    - Photos 1-8 (Box 88, Folder 356)
      Scope and Contents note
      Photo 8 is accompanied by a piece of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 1: KLI President Kennedy at White House (with Sarah Anderson) and "conversation" written on back, February 16,1963
      Photo 2: KLI Herb Fineman, Early 1970's
      Photo 3: KLI; Hon. Chas Rangel, NY; Bro. Walter Washington; Hon. Ernest Moneal (Mayor of New Orleans); and Harold R. Simms (Vice President National Urban League) at the AMA Eastern Regional Convention, 1971
      Photo 4: Photo of city (Philadelphia?), February 13,1975
      Photo 5: KLI, Lee Donaldson, "Doc", Senator Bob Fleming, February 1972
      Photo 6: General Matthew Ridgeway reviewing the troops at the Point - Ft. Pitt Museum, June 13, 1975
      Photo 7: KLI at desk, 1977
      Photo 8: KLI, Rep. Joseph C. Manmiller and Thelma Mariana (retiring House Official Reporter), December 13, 1977
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 357)
      Photo 9-18A: KLI at podium, 1977-1978
      Photo 19: KLI's empty desk, 1977-1978
      Photo 20-22: KLI at his desk, 1977-1978
      Photo 23-25A: KLI at desk, 1977-1978
      Photo 26: KLI with shovels, 1977-1978
      Photo 27-31: KLI with 3 others, 1977-1978
      Photo 32: KLI speaking on the Black presence in PA at the William Penn Museum, Harrisburg, PA., February 6, 1977
      Photo 33-34: KLI, 1977-1978
      Photo 35-35A: KLI handing over golden gavel, 1977-1978
      Photo 36-37A: KLI macramé, 1977-1978
      Photo 38-38A: KLI walking into his office, 1977-78
      Photo 39: KLI at lunch, 1977-78
      Photo 40-41: Mrs. Cathryn Irvis, 1977-78
      Photo 42-43: Rufus Lynch, 1977-78
      Photo 44-45: Woman at KLI's desk, 1977-78
      Photo 46-47: unknown, 1977-78
      Photo 48: KLI at his desk, 1977-78
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 358)
      Photo 49-50: KLI Mrs. Cathy Irvis getting awards at "Blue Ribbon Citizens' Committee of ?" dinner, January 15, 1978
      Photo 51: Mrs. Cathy Irvis, January 15, 1978
      Photo 52: KLI, Byrd Brown, Dr. Wesley Posvar, Dr. Larry Howard at the Presentation of Homer S. Brown Papers, March 3, 1978
      Photo 53: KLI with Kid Gavilan, April, 1978
      Photo 54-57: KLI with Chuck Chietto(?) putting up new flags at the New Field airstrip, May, 1978
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 359)
      Photo 58 is accompanied by a piece of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 58: KLI President Jimmy Carter shaking hands, autographed, September 23, 1978
      Photo 59-68: KLI in reception line with Richard Caliguiri and others greeting President Jimmy Carter at Greater Pittsburgh Airport, September 23, 1978
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 360)
      Photo 69 is accompanied by correspondence and Photo 76 is accompanied by clippings that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 69: KLI speaking at the Pittsburgh Hilton for the Kennedy Lawrence Dinner (Allegheny Co. Democratic Committee), October 16, 1978
      Photo 70: KLI, Mrs. Cathy Irvis, Secretary Harris, October 28, 1978
      Photo 71-73: KLI, October 28, 1978
      Photo 74: Jack Seltzer KLI in Harrisburg announcing special election after the death of Frank Meloskey, November 27, 1978
      Photo 75: Richard Caligiuri Mrs. Cathy Irvis, December 12, 1978
      Photo 76: Placing Cornerstone for Riverview Children's Center (Valley News Dispatch), 1979
      Photo 77: Mrs. Jean C. Young (National Chairperson IYC) with Mrs. Cathy Irvis, 1979
      Photo 78: Mrs. Cathryn L. Irvis at Hershey Expo, September 17, 1979
      Photo 79: Mrs. Cathy Irvis, Governor Dick Thornburgh, Mrs. Ginny Thornburgh, Malcolm Lazin, Judy Willam Henry (mascot) at Hostel Hershey Country Club, PA Exposition, International Year of the Child, September 17, 1979
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 361)
      Photos 85-87 are accompanied by pieces of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 80: KLI at Phoenix Shopping Plaza (Shop N' Save) in the Hill District, 1980
      Photo 81-83: KLI goofing around on the set of "Chiller Theatre" (Channel 11), hosted by his friend Bill Cardille, 1980
      Photo 84: KLI with Carter/Mondale paraphernalia, 1980
      Photo 85-86: KLI speaking at Justin Johnson's induction ceremony, December 16, 1980
      Photo 87: KLI, Richard Caligiuri, John D. Locton (President Warner Amex Cable Commission, Inc.), LaDonna Lewis (graduate Bidwell, Inc.), March, 1981
      Photo 88: KLI Olga ? at Democratic St. Patrick's Day Fundraiser, March 16, 1981
      Photo 89: KLI with Jim M. at St. Patrick's Day Fundraiser, March 16, 1981
      Photo 90: KLI with Nigerian Delegation in Harrisburg, March 24, 1981
      Photo 91: KLI young friend of Rep. Williams, 1982
    - Photos (Box 88, Folder 362)
      Photos 92-103 are accompanied by negatives, Photo 113 is accompanied by is clippings, and Photo 114 is accompanied by a piece of correspondence that can be found in the Photo Correspondence and Clippings File (Box 37, Folder 386)
      Photo 92-93: Steps inside Capital, 1983
      Photo 94: Rotunda inside Capital, 1983